

# RIZQY PRASTYA ARI NUGROHO

# WEB DEV & GAME DEV

- Kudus, Jawa Tengah
- rizqynugroho88@gmail.com
- +62 8985 6654 98

#### Socials

- rizqy.pan
- rizqyn9
- in rizqynugroho9

## Portfolio (

http://portfolio.rbot-rizqy.online

## Professional Summary

Diligent web developer with better experience in implement and developing user interfaces, testing, debugging and deploying. Not only as web developer, i have some experience to created game & multiplayer game with Unity. Now i'm starting to learn DevOps focussing in DevOps cycle, and succeed in implementing containerizing and apps scaling with Kubernetes and Docker.

## Education

2018 - Present

#### STMM "MMTC" Yogyakarta

Game Technology

## Work Experience

2020

Web Dev in Dinas Arsip Semarang

2020 - Present

Founder & CEO of R-Dev Studio

2020 - Present

Freelancer Full Stack Developer

## Internship Experience

2020

Project Lead at PT. Sinarmas ( Asset Management )

## Technical Skill Set

DevOps	Tools
Docker	Unity
Kubernetes	Visual Studio
Jenkins	Visual Studio Code
Jest	Git
Nginx	Zsh
	Docker Kubernetes Jenkins Jest

**Back End** 

#### Front End

SASS Canvas

React Express.js
Next.js Nest.js
Three.js npm
Redux Yarn
Tailwind

#### **DBMS**

Redis MongoDB PostgreSQL Elastic Search